man. Yeah.
>> To this point in your career, what does
it mean to still be able to have them
still want you to have them still bring
you back like this?
>> Yeah. Uh John, I I honestly think you
said it best just with the word want.
Um, I think, um, I think when you play a
position and whenever you have something
to offer up to the team, it's just the
coolest compliment for professional
athlete or I actually love how DQ always
says it, professional competitor, uh,
that they want you. Um, and I think just
as I get as as I get older, the longer
I've played, you just realize like I I
remember whenever I was first trying to
crack the league and first trying to get
in and uh I am just I am just so
grateful and so honored uh that that I'm
wanted by these guys. And I told DQ and
AP uh you know came up and gave me a hug
and bringing the kids a big hug and I
just said, "Man, I I just have so much
fun playing for you guys and I I'm just
honored that you guys asked me to come
back." So,
>> has it like ignited anything in you to
want to play longer than maybe you even
imagined?
>> Um, yeah. You know, I think the I think
the the the great part about uh playing
professional ball with some with some
serious gratitude is uh there's a whole
lot of freedom in that where uh all I
know is we report in April now and I
just can't wait to come see everybody
again and start practicing again and
fire up another season. Um, I I think I
think you talk about like a fuel and a
fire. I know a lot of guys have careers
and they never get the chance to make
the kind of run that we made a couple of
years ago. That was I I will just
remember that feeling the rest of my
life. And the feeling in those winds and
things like that. So there's a there's
multiple multiple fires and multiple
fuel sources, I guess you could say.
Yeah.
>> Tong congratulations. You said the want
is is key. I it's hard to imagine you
playing anywhere else. Could you I I
don't know for you how for when you knew
this was going to happen. But does your
brain ever go like well I I don't know
maybe I go somewhere else or
>> um you know it it really doesn't. Um and
thankfully it's because it never it's
never gotten to that point. Um it's uh
um you know we said that we're kind of
going on the word want a little bit but
whenever I got cut uh for the second
time by the Chicago Bears in 2014 in
training camp uh I got claimed on the
waiver wire here in Washington and that
was the first time that that want really
like kind of I don't know just really
stuck with me where it was like a team
it almost felt like I had gotten drafted
in a way where it was just like oh hey
I'm now up for grabs abs and instead of
me clearing waiverss and then figuring
out if I could go try out somewhere, get
a workout, it was like, no, you
immediately became a part of this team.
And so, um, I I hope I hope a lot of
people feel the same way you do about
like, hey, can't imagine you playing
anywhere else. I know I can't and I
don't want to. And, uh, I'm just excited
to come back for another year. So, yeah.
Tres, uh could you talk a little bit
about what you have enjoyed the most
about uh playing for this team because
you've had multiple uh coaches that
you've played for, but what resonates
the most about coming back and playing
for this team right now?
>> Yeah, I um I I hope there's I hope
there's one day whenever I'm done
playing that there's there's a way for
me to to be able to get to have some
message out there. uh and get it across
to the fans in some way. Um but you get
you get one career when you play in the
NFL and you don't know how long it's
going to be. And uh I'm I'm the I'm the
punter for the Washington Commanders.
And the relationships and the stories
and the memories and the like going out
to dinner with the family and a fan
stops over just to say, "Hey, like that
this is this has got to be my
experience. Like this has got to be my
career." and the fans have made that so
special. Um, you know, being the punter
for a franchise and making plays with
some of my best friends on the field and
the times that we're pinning teams on
the one or we flip the field when we're
backed up and you just kind of get those
like momentum plays going and things
like that. I could probably make a long
long list of things that uh that really
stick with me the most. But but I think
that's that's it for me is the fans like
this for this long. It's been been uh it
has definitely been a lot of fun. Yeah.
>> Hey Tres, congratulations. I guess we
need to add Pro Bowler
Trese. How was your Pro Bowl experience?
>> It was really good. They uh they did an
awesome job in San Francisco. We um are
uh we got to take the kids everywhere.
Um it was fun. We called it elevator
roulette. Uh my son's old enough now to
be doing some fantasy football with the
other neighborhood boys and you know
half of that fantasy football league is
walking around that hotel and so when
we'd be taking the elevator down and it
would stop on the floor you didn't know
if it was going to open up to you know
Micah Parsons or it was going to open up
to Dak or like some of these guys and Bo
got to introduce himself to everybody
and so it it's just uh how they how they
let you bring all the families and uh
make it a whole family affair was it was
really Cool. Yeah, thank you for asking.
Yeah,
>> T, just curious because I heard it. It
sounded really loud in that other
building. What was the surprise like or
do you have family, friends? What was
what was going on there?
>> Yep. There is a uh there's a very
there's a very uh very certain song and
there's a very certain um I wouldn't
call it a dance move, but a motion that
is made in the special teams rooms
whenever we really start getting fired
up a little bit first thing in the
mornings, you know, leading into the
weekend. And uh it was funny when we
were walking and looking through the
glass doors, I could see everybody in
there and I could kind of kind of hear
some loud music going and then when
those doors opened up and I heard the
song and everybody was doing the dance
move or motion, if you will. Uh I just
joined right in. And I think my my wife
and my kids were like, "Oh, uh dad may
be a little different when he leaves the
house here." So, but uh but it uh it it
was just and as soon as I jumped in,
everybody got all excited and uh it's
yeah, like they they don't have to do
that. Uh they they don't have to do
that. That's just another another thing
that what makes that that building and
those guys over there so special is uh
just doing little things like that to
take the time to make that special for
our family. And now we've got pictures
for year to come, years to come, videos
for years to come. And uh yeah, big big
memories guy. So, that's a that's a good
one. Yeah.
>> Good evening, Trust. Congrats.
>> Thank you.
>> Um, obviously you're happy, your family,
very very big day for you and your
family, but I'm sure Coach Iso, uh,
Tyler Owens, Percy Butler, Revo, among
the others who are very happy. Uh, just
I know you've talked about it before,
but just kind of how you feel about
being part of that collective of guys.
>> Yeah. Um uh when I was fortunate enough
to get voted into the Pro Bowl this
year, um we went out and had a big punt
team dinner and I just told the guys, I
was like, "Hey, I I'm the one who gets
to go to San Francisco, I'm the one, you
know, who gets to go do the experience
and have a lot of fun." And thankfully
all of those guys were sitting there
around that dinner table. And I just
wanted to take the time to tell them, I
was like, "Guys, I do not I do not go
like if you guys are not on this squad."
and how coach IO has that like that room
and those guys like the amount of fire
like like obviously we lost way more
games than we wanted to this year but
whenever you got into those special
teams rooms and you knew that you just
went out and whooped on somebody else's
unit a little bit like it's just this
game within the game and how like how he
fires us all up not to mention in my
opinion I have the best coverage guys on
planet Earth and they just keep getting
better and they're just selfless guys
that love playing. They're all fired up.
I think I'm competitive and then I watch
them play ball and I'm like, "All right,
maybe there's a level I could get to."
So, uh it it's just uh it's really cool
being a part of a group of guys like
that.
>> Tres, not just this team, not just this
organization, but the DMV community
really loves and embraces you as well.
For you to be coming back, signing a new
deal, what does this whole DMV community
mean to you? Yeah. Um, you know, I I
I I
a couple of years ago, um, I've shared
this story before, so forgive me if you
guys have heard this, but the best way
that I could put it is we have we've got
to make some awesome plays on the punt
team for years and watching just
watching the fans like get excited
about, you know, a big play on the punt
team. That that's pretty surreal. Like
for me, it's just it's cool to like add
that momentum and that's what we want to
do on special teams. But I'll never
forget uh two years ago whenever we were
playing the Atlanta Falcons and we were
we were really trying to clinch that uh
last playoff spot or one of the playoff
spots and and we were losing if at
halftime if memory serves me correctly
and our fans were like loudly cheering
us on and I just I couldn't I could like
I I'm getting chills thinking about it
now. It was so cool to see where, you
know, man, we've had like some really
tough years in the past and just like
you see anywhere else across the NFL,
you know, fans will voice their opinion
about how things are going and, you
know, maybe we're not making the plays
we should be, all these different things
like that. But it was it was like I just
saw I saw like the community and the fan
base just completely just be all gas.
like it was just and uh and and I it
makes it so much fun to start another
season and so I'm I'm very appreciative
to been able to have seen that, you
know, in my career and to see this
excitement and things like that. Yeah.
Yeah.
>> Hey Tres, back here. Congrats on
everything. um you know, for you to to
think back to when you first got here
and when you kind of put that pen to
paper today, did you ever think you'd be
sitting here at this point, like playing
here this long doing this much with this
franchise?
>> Yeah. Uh you know, my my agent, Kelly
Masters, she came uh out for this
signing. Um it was the first time she's
been out out here uh for a signing and
she was there when I signed my first
contract with the Chicago Bears. Uh, but
one of my favorite stories that I always
tell Kelly is whenever I was coming out
of college as a punter for Oklahoma, I
only there was only one agent that
reached out to me that wanted to
represent me moving forward and it was
her. And uh, and she and she talked
about me being a lefty. She was very
realistic of what to expect, you know,
as a punter and trying to make it and
things like that. And so now we were
laughing driving in the car over here
and I was just like, how about that?
Signing on for year 13, you know, at the
same spot. So, um, I hope you guys get
my like general theme and general
message, but it's kind of hard every
which way you turn, there's something to
be grateful for. So,
>> real quick, you mentioned that run a
couple years ago, or not this past, but
the one before. Um, I just remember
talking to you about that smile on your
face every time you walked in the locker
room. Basically, that permanent smile
the whole season. How much of a role
does this contract and this decision,
how much does like the fact of maybe
getting to do that again this coming
season play in this?
>> Oh, 100%. that is uh
other than just other than just loving
competing and you know being thankful
for the gift the Lord gave me to punt a
football I the the like those games and
those playoffs and like winning and then
moving on and then all of a sudden
there's less teams left in the NFL and
then you win you move on again there's
even le and like that was just I I'll
never forget when we were practicing for
the NFC championship I looked at Tyler
and I go there's only four teams doing
this right now. Like this is wild. Uh
and and this year, you know, obviously
we got eliminated and I was watching the
playoffs on the uh on the couch. I was
like, "Yeah, playing them is a lot
better than this." So, uh it is uh I I
think but I think that that's something
man I that's I trust AP and DQ so much.
Um just how how they've I mean what what
they've done for this whole community
and for the fan base, what they've done
for us as players, how they care about
us as guys. But that's something like
I'll put I'll put my coins with them
that that we'll be rolling it back out
there. Yeah.
>> Thanks a lot, guys.
>> Guys aren't getting rid of me yet now.
>> It was It wasn't San Francisco. It was
here.